PT	AU	BA	BE	GP	AF	BF	CA	TI	SO	SE	BS	LA	DT	CT	CY	CL	SP	HO	DE	ID	AB	C1	RP	EM	RI	OI	FU	FX	CR	NR	TC	Z9	U1	U2	PU	PI	PA	SN	EI	BN	J9	JI	PD	PY	VL	IS	PN	SU	SI	MA	BP	EP	AR	DI	D2	EA	EY	PG	WC	SC	GA	UT	PM	OA	HC	HP	DA
S	Kan, C; Chen, Y; Leonelli, F; Yang, H			IEEE	Kan, Chen; Chen, Yun; Leonelli, Fabio; Yang, Hui			Mobile Sensing and Network Analytics for Realizing Smart Automated Systems towards Health Internet of Things	2015 INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON AUTOMATION SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (CASE)	IEEE International Conference on Automation Science and Engineering		English	Proceedings Paper	IEEE International Conference on Automation Science and Engineering (CASE)	AUG 24-28, 2015	Gothenburg, SWEDEN	IEEE, IEEE Robotics & Automation Society, ABB, Chalmers, Wingquist Laboratory, City of Gothenburg, Cognibotics, Kuka, Volvo, AREUS, Information and communication technology				Internet of Things (IoT) provides an unprecedented opportunity to realize smart automated systems such as smart manufacturing, smart city and smart home in the past few years. Pervasive sensing and mobile technology deployed in large-scale IoT systems lead to the accumulation of big data. In particular, wearable biosensing accelerates human-centered computing for smart health management. However, limited work has been done to develop advanced IoT technologies for smart monitoring and control of heart health. There is an urgent need to develop a new IoT technology specific to the heart, namely Internet of Hearts (IOH) that will enable and assist (1) the acquisition of electrocardiogram (ECG) signals pertinent to space-time cardiac dynamics at anytime anywhere; (2) real-time management and compact representation of multi-sensor signals; (3) big data analytics in large-scale IoT contexts. This paper presents a new technology of Mobile and E-Network Smart Health (MESH), which is composed of 4 components as follows: 1) Mobile-based ECG sensing device; 2) Space-time representation of cardiac electrical activity; 3) Optimal model-based representation of ECG signals; 4) Dynamic network embedding for disease pattern recognition. Our preliminary experimental results demonstrated that network analytics is efficient and effective for smart health management in IoT contexts. The MESH technology shows strong potentials to provide an indispensable and enabling tool for realizing smart heart health and wellbeing for the population worldwide.	[Kan, Chen; Chen, Yun; Leonelli, Fabio; Yang, Hui] Univ S Florida, Complex Syst Monitoring Modeling & Anal Lab, Tampa, FL 33620 USA	Yang, H (reprint author), Univ S Florida, Complex Syst Monitoring Modeling & Anal Lab, Tampa, FL 33620 USA.	huiyang@usf.edu					Auricchio A, 2004, CIRCULATION, V109, P1133, DOI 10.1161/01.CIR.0000118502.91105.F6; Deyle ER, 2011, PLOS ONE, V6, DOI 10.1371/journal.pone.0018295; DOWER GE, 1988, J ELECTROCARDIOL, V21, pS182, DOI 10.1016/0022-0736(88)90090-8; LIU G, 2013, BIOMEDICAL HLTH INFO, V17, P484, DOI DOI 10.1109/JBHI.2013.2243842; YANG H, 2011, BIOMEDICAL ENG IEEE, V58, P339, DOI DOI 10.1109/TBME.2010.2063704; Yang H., 2012, BIOMEDICAL ENG ONLIN, V11; YANG H, 2013, AUTOMATION SCI ENG I, V10, P938, DOI DOI 10.1109/TASE.2013.2263497; Yang H., 2012, International PCT Patent, Patent No. [WO2014043216 A1, 2014043216]; Zhu C, 2011, IEEE T SYST MAN CY A, V41, P569, DOI 10.1109/TSMCA.2010.2093883	9	9	9	3	10	IEEE	NEW YORK	345 E 47TH ST, NEW YORK, NY 10017 USA	2161-8070		978-1-4673-8183-3	IEEE INT CON AUTO SC			2015							1072	1077						6	Automation & Control Systems	Automation & Control Systems	BF2BL	WOS:000380453000177					2019-04-08	
