PT	AU	BA	BE	GP	AF	BF	CA	TI	SO	SE	BS	LA	DT	CT	CY	CL	SP	HO	DE	ID	AB	C1	RP	EM	RI	OI	FU	FX	CR	NR	TC	Z9	U1	U2	PU	PI	PA	SN	EI	BN	J9	JI	PD	PY	VL	IS	PN	SU	SI	MA	BP	EP	AR	DI	D2	EA	EY	PG	WC	SC	GA	UT	PM	OA	HC	HP	DA
B	Singh, VP; Deshmukh, U			IEEE	Singh, Vineet Pratap; Deshmukh, Urmila			FACEBOOK BASED HOME APPLIANCES SECURITY CONTROL AND MONITORING USING RASPBERRY PI 3	PROCEEDINGS OF THE 2018 SECOND INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON INVENTIVE COMMUNICATION AND COMPUTATIONAL TECHNOLOGIES (ICICCT)			English	Proceedings Paper	International Conference on Inventive Communication and Computational Technologies (ICICCT)	APR 20-21, 2018	Coimbatore, INDIA	IEEE, Ranganathan Engn Coll		Facebook interface; microcontroller; Raspberry Pi; sensor		The real-time boot device status was created in various fields. The new innovation is important to prepare the general measure of state data every day. Inventive innovation that has been recently utilized to prepare a lot of information is cloud computing. So in this work a model is intended to monitor and control devices using Facebook in a intelligent home environment. In the proposed methodology, the preloaded Facebook Ethernet device verified and collects and stores home device information and sends the information to the Facebook user page. This information can be shared with a customer or through social networking sites to meet the user's home automation. Flexible and with the help of the open source and camera chassis packages needed to manage Facebook and embedded password processor management system time application. The created picture facilitates the utilization of home automation with Facebook and can be improved in the future by validating bio metrics. The clint or user can control smart home applications by sending commands to your Facebook account.	[Singh, Vineet Pratap] Indira Coll Engn & Management, Dept Elect & Telecommun, Commun Engn, Pune, Maharashtra, India; [Deshmukh, Urmila] Indira Coll Engn & Management, Dept Elect & Telecom, Pune, Maharashtra, India	Singh, VP (reprint author), Indira Coll Engn & Management, Dept Elect & Telecommun, Commun Engn, Pune, Maharashtra, India.	singhvineetk@gmail.com; urmila.deshmukh@indiraicem.ac.in					Alheraish A, 2004, IEEE T CONSUM ELECTR, V50, P1087, DOI 10.1109/TCE.2004.1362503; [Anonymous], SICE ANN C, V3, p2824 ; Badar Rumana, 2015, INT J RECENT INNOVAT, V3; BarisYuksekkaya A., IEEE T CONSUMER ELEC, V52, P837; Byun  J., 2012, IEEE T CONSUMER ELEC, V58; Gaikwad Jyoti, 2017, INT RES J ENG TECHNO, V04; Muminur Rahman Md., 2017, INT J INNOVATIVE RES, V4, P12; Teymourzadeh Rozita, 2015, INT J COMPUTER APPL, V116, P18; Van Der Werff M., 2005, IEE Mobility Conference 2005. The Second International Conference on Mobile Technology, Applications and Systems; Xiaojing Y., 2011, INT C COMP SCI NETW	10	0	0	0	0	IEEE	NEW YORK	345 E 47TH ST, NEW YORK, NY 10017 USA			978-1-5386-1974-2				2018							487	491						5	Computer Science, Theory & Methods; Engineering, Electrical & Electronic; Telecommunications	Computer Science; Engineering; Telecommunications	BL8FP	WOS:000456251700094					2019-04-08	
S	Pillai, AS; Isha, TB		Krishnan, N; Karthikeyan, M		Pillai, Anju S.; Isha, T. B.			A Power-aware Multiprocessor Based Laboratory Automation and Resource Management System	2014 IEEE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON COMPUTATIONAL INTELLIGENCE AND COMPUTING RESEARCH (IEEE ICCIC)	IEEE International Conference on Computational Intelligence and Computing Research		English	Proceedings Paper	5th IEEE International Conference on Computational Intelligence and Computing Research (IEEE ICCIC)	DEC 18-20, 2014	Park Coll Engn & Tekhnol, Coimbatore, INDIA	IEEE, IEEE Podhigai Subsect, IEEE SIPCICOM, PARK Grp Inst	Park Coll Engn & Tekhnol	Automation systems; power-aware systems; power consumption reduction; multiprocessor systems; embedded processors	ENERGY	Due to the advancements in technology, new and complex techniques are explored and are becoming a common practice. Automation systems are prevalent in all application domains whether it is home automation or factory automation. This paper presents the design and development of a Laboratory Automation and Resource Management System (LARMS). The developed system consists of heterogeneous multiprocessor systems connected and communicated to be a part of distributed networked embedded systems. The main features of LARMS are: automatic lab access through bio-metric sensors, real time clock, automatic device control based on the ambient environment conditions and human presence and the central communication controller to supervise and coordinate the entire system functioning. LARMS is implemented using PIC16F877 microcontrollers and ARM7 TDMI controller. The main contribution of the work is the implementation of a power-aware solution for LARMS. The simulation results manifest the energy solutions provided by the proposed automation and resource management system.	[Pillai, Anju S.; Isha, T. B.] Amrita Vishwa Vidyapeetham, Dept Elect & Elect Engn, Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India	Pillai, AS (reprint author), Amrita Vishwa Vidyapeetham, Dept Elect & Elect Engn, Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India.	s_anju@cb.amrita.edu; tb_isha@cb.amrita.edu					Camarinha-Matos LuisM, 2000, ADV NETWORKED ENTERP, V53; Demetriou DW, 2009, BUILD SIMUL-CHINA, V2, P197, DOI 10.1007/s12273-009-9320-z; Dounis AI, 2009, RENEW SUST ENERG REV, V13, P1246, DOI 10.1016/j.rser.2008.09.015; Hassan Syed Zulqadar, 2014, INT J RES IJR, V1, P751; Mechs S, 2012, 17 IEEE C EM TECHN F, P1; Mechs S., 2012, VDI BERICHTE AUTOMAT, P251; Mechs S, 2012, P AMER CONTR CONF, P5310	7	1	1	0	0	IEEE	NEW YORK	345 E 47TH ST, NEW YORK, NY 10017 USA	2471-7851		978-1-4799-3975-6	IEEE I C COMP INT CO			2014							1219	1222						4	Computer Science, Interdisciplinary Applications; Computer Science, Theory & Methods; Engineering, Electrical & Electronic	Computer Science; Engineering	BI5AB	WOS:000412179000252					2019-04-08	
